<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[D'Catasus Documentation]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.png</url><title>D'Catasus Documentation</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:30:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:30:40 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[index]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>]]></description><link>index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">index.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:28:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Admin]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br><br><br><br><br>Operators are Net2's way of handling permissions. Basic user editing and management involves handing adding tokens to the user so that they can open a door with those tokens. Operators can log in to the software themselves. Everything an operator does in the software will be logged, including signing in. Below is a table which details the operators permission levels and what they are capable of doing.<br><img alt="Images/OPERATOR_PERMISSIONS.png" src="images\operator_permissions.png"><br>An operator can be:<br><br>Operators are added by clicking on the Net2 operators tab and clicking either New operator in the list view, or the New operator option in the tool bar. A user, operator permission, and password is then chosen. <br><img alt="GIFS/ADD_OPERATOR.gif" src="gifs\add_operator.gif"><br><br>Operators are edited by clicking on the operator in question and clicking edit. Changing the operator to any of the options except for None will give that operator those permissions. <br><img alt="GIFS/EDIT_OPERATOR.gif" src="gifs\edit_operator.gif"><br><br>Operators are deleted by clicking on the operator in question and clicking edit. Changing the operator to have the None role will remove all permissions from the operator and they will cease to be listed as such.<br><img alt="GIFS/DELETE_OPERATOR.gif" src="gifs\delete_operator.gif"><br><br><br>Time zones dictate at what time certain events can happen. For example, a door might stay open during working hours. Or someone might only be able to open the door <br><br>Creating a timezone involves navigating to the timezone tab in the list view on the left, and then clicking on New timezone in either the list view on the right, or the toolbar at the top.<br>
<img alt="GIFS/CREATE_TIMEZONE.gif" src="gifs\create_timezone.gif"><br><br>There are a few option when it comes to deleting a timezone:<br>
<br>From the timezone tab, right clicking on a specific timezone will provide an option to delete. 
<br>Alternatively once a timezone is selected, the delete button on the bottom right of the application can be pressed. 
<br>Lastly, the option to delete is shown when a timezone is right clicked from the list view on the left of the application after the timezone tab has been expanded.<br>
<img alt="GIFS/DELETE_TIMEZONE.gif" src="gifs\delete_timezone.gif">
<br><br>Timezones can be edited by double clicking on the specific timezone in either the list view on the left of the application, or the list view shown when the timezone tab has been selected. <br><img alt="GIFS/EDIT_TIMEZONE.gif" src="gifs\edit_timezone.gif"><br><br><br>Doors refer to all the control units that are connected to the server<br><br>Doors can be edited by navigating to the door tab and clicking on the specific door. Alternatively, in a door can be selected in the expanded list view on the left. Afterwards, a user with appropriate permissions can make changes to a variety of fields in the door including the Auto-unlock time schedule. Reader details and Operating mode are usually installation specific and should not be touched in most cases. Any changes made to the door must be saved by clicking the apply button at the top right of the application.<br>
<img alt="EDIT_DOOR.gif" src="gifs\edit_door.gif">]]></description><link>paxton-net2-user-guide.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Paxton Net2 User Guide.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:25:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="images\operator_permissions.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="images\operator_permissions.png"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reolink User Guide]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>reolink-user-guide.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Reolink User Guide.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:26:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>