<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[D'Catasus Documentation]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.png</url><title>D'Catasus Documentation</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 02:42:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 02:42:43 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[index]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>]]></description><link>index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">index.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:28:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Admin]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br><br><br>Users are added by navigating to the user tab and clicking on new user, either in the list view displayed on the right, or in the toolbar displayed at the top. <br>User information can be added in the Add user pop-up, this information varies from personal identifying information, to information like the pin which is used to open gates. <br>FOR KEYPAD ACCESS a pin MUST be assigned to the user. When a user opens the gate using their pin, it will log that access in the system. <br><img alt="add_user.gif" src="gifs\add_user.gif"><br><br>To delete a user, select the user as if you were going to edit them, then click the Void user button at the bottom of the application. Voiding the user means to bar them from all doors, giving them the no access <a data-href="#Access Level Permissions" href="about:blank#Access_Level_Permissions" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Access Level Permissions</a>. Once a user has been voided, they can then be deleted by pressing the Delete record button.<br>
<img alt="delete_user.gif" src="gifs\delete_user.gif"><br><br>A user can be edited by double clicking on that user in either the list view on the left, or the list view on the right once the Users tab has been clicked. You can change personal identifying now, AND assign Access level permissions. <a data-href="#Access level permissions" href="about:blank#Access_level_permissions" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Access level permissions</a> dictate what doors the user can open at what time.<br>
<img alt="edit_user.gif" src="gifs\edit_user.gif"><br><br><br>Operators are Net2's way of handling permissions. Basic user editing and management involves handing adding tokens to the user so that they can open a door with those tokens. Operators can log in to the software themselves. Everything an operator does in the software will be logged, including signing in. Below is a table which details the operators permission levels and what they are capable of doing.<br><img alt="operator_permissions.png" src="images\operator_permissions.png"><br>An operator can be:<br><br>Operators are added by clicking on the Net2 operators tab and clicking either New operator in the list view, or the New operator option in the tool bar. A user, operator permission, and password is then chosen. Before an operator role can be created for someone, they must have a user created for them.  Adding a user is described in <a data-href="#User Management" href="about:blank#User_Management" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">User Management</a><br><img alt="add_operator.gif" src="gifs\add_operator.gif"><br><br>Operators are edited by clicking on the operator in question and clicking edit. Changing the operator to any of the options except for None will give that operator those permissions. <br><img alt="edit_operator.gif" src="gifs\edit_operator.gif"><br><br>Operators are deleted by clicking on the operator in question and clicking edit. Changing the operator to have the None role will remove all permissions from the operator and they will cease to be listed as such.<br><img alt="delete_operator.gif" src="gifs\delete_operator.gif"><br><br><br>Access Level Permissions dictate which doors a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="User Management" data-href="#User Management" href="about:blank#User_Management" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">user</a> can open and at what time. An access level pairs <a data-href="#Doors" href="about:blank#Doors" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Doors</a> with <a data-href="#Time Zones" href="about:blank#Time_Zones" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">Time Zones</a>. Each access level pairs each door with one timezone. The Cleaners Access level shown below does the following:<br>
<br>Allows the Outside world and Car park doors to be opened All day, every day
<br>Only allows the Factory, Meeting room, and Reception doors to be opened during the designated cleaning Timezone
<br>Does not allow the Stores or Offices to be opened at any time.<br>
<img alt="cleaners_access_level.png" src="images\cleaners_access_level.png">
<br><br>Access levels are added by clicking on the Access levels tab and clicking either New access level in the list view, or the New access level option in the tool bar<br><img alt="add_access_level.gif" src="gifs\add_access_level.gif"><br><br>There are a few option when it comes to deleting an access level:<br>
<br>From the Access levels tab, right clicking on a specific access level will provide an option to delete. 
<br>Alternatively once a access level is selected, the delete button on the bottom right of the application can be pressed. 
<br>Lastly, the option to delete is shown when an access level is right clicked from the list view on the left of the application after the access levels tab has been expanded. 
<br><img alt="delete_access_level.gif" src="gifs\delete_access_level.gif"><br><br>To edit an access level, double click on the access level in the list view on the left or in the Access levels tab. Once the access level has been selected, all doors in the system will be displayed on the left of the editing section. On the right of each door is the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Time Zones" data-href="#Time Zones" href="about:blank#Time_Zones" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">timezone</a> that the access level will be able to open that door.<br>
<img alt="edit_access.gif" src="gifs\edit_access.gif"><br><br><br>Time zones dictate at what time certain events can happen. For example, a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Doors" data-href="#Doors" href="about:blank#Doors" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">door</a> might stay open during working hours. Or someone might only be able to open the door.<br><br>Creating a timezone involves navigating to the timezone tab in the list view on the left, and then clicking on New timezone in either the list view on the right, or the toolbar at the top.<br>
<img alt="create_timezone.gif" src="gifs\create_timezone.gif"><br><br>There are a few option when it comes to deleting a timezone:<br>
<br>From the timezone tab, right clicking on a specific timezone will provide an option to delete. 
<br>Alternatively once a timezone is selected, the delete button on the bottom right of the application can be pressed. 
<br>Lastly, the option to delete is shown when a timezone is right clicked from the list view on the left of the application after the timezone tab has been expanded.<br>
<img alt="delete_timezone.gif" src="gifs\delete_timezone.gif">
<br><br>Timezones can be edited by double clicking on the specific timezone in either the list view on the left of the application, or the list view shown when the timezone tab has been selected. The Public holiday section section dictates what happens on any user defined holidays.<br><img alt="edit_timezone.gif" src="gifs\edit_timezone.gif"><br><br>To create or delete a custom day, press the options menu on the top toolbar, then the custom days listing. Once the custom days pop up has opened, a custom day can be created by selecting the specific date range desired and description, then clicking the add button. A custom day can be deleting by selecting the custom day in the list view, and clicking the Delete button.<br><img alt="custom_days.gif" src="gifs\custom_days.gif"><br><br><br>Doors refer to all the control units that are connected to the server<br><br>Doors can be edited by navigating to the door tab and clicking on the specific door. Alternatively, in a door can be selected in the expanded list view on the left. Afterwards, a user with appropriate permissions can make changes to a variety of fields in the door including the Auto-unlock time schedule. Reader details and Operating mode are usually installation specific and should not be touched in most cases. Any changes made to the door must be saved by clicking the apply button at the top right of the application.<br>
<img alt="edit_door.gif" src="gifs\edit_door.gif"><br><br>A normal user would be an <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Operators (Application Permissions)" data-href="#Operators (Application Permissions)" href="about:blank#Operators_(Application_Permissions)" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">operator</a> that is unable to make changes to the software. The main purpose to access the software then, would be to open and close a door.<br><br>If an <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Operators (Application Permissions)" data-href="#Operators (Application Permissions)" href="about:blank#Operators_(Application_Permissions)" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">operator</a> has some kind administrative position, they will have the Open door option on the toolbar at the top. By pressing this button they can select the doors they wish to open or close, then select whether they want to:<br>
<br>open the door normally
<br>open the door for a specified time
<br>open the door and hold it open
<br>close the door.<br>
They complete the interaction by clicking on the Finish button at the bottom right
<br><img alt="open_doors_client.gif" src="gifs\open_doors_client.gif"><br><br>Even an <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Operators (Application Permissions)" data-href="#Operators (Application Permissions)" href="about:blank#Operators_(Application_Permissions)" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">operator</a> with the most basic of permissions has the ability to open the door through the web application. Once logged in to the application, the user clicks on Open Door, then selects the specific <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="Doors" data-href="#Doors" href="about:blank#Doors" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">door</a> they want to by clicking on the Open Door next to that door's name. <br><img alt="open_doors_web.gif" src="gifs\open_doors_web.gif">]]></description><link>paxton-net2-user-guide.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Paxton Net2 User Guide.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 02:42:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="gifs\add_user.gif" length="0" type="image/gif"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="gifs\add_user.gif"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reolink User Guide]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>reolink-user-guide.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Reolink User Guide.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:26:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>